[ Woman ] Uncle Michael , please don 't hurt me .
[ Screaming ]
[ Screaming Continues ]
[ Gasping , Screaming ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Screaming Continues ]
[ Gasping , Screaming ]
Oh , no !
[ Rapid Breathing ]
- Push ! - [ Screams ]
- Push . - [ Screaming ] Oh , God , it 's coming !
- Jamie ... Jamie , one push ! - It 's coming ! [ Screams ]
[ Screaming ]
- Push , push . Push . - [ Screaming ]
- [ Screaming ] - [ Low , Heavy Breathing ]
[ Baby Crying ]
[ Screaming ] No !
[ Sobs ]
Please give him to me .
Please give him to me . Please .
[ Gurgles , Grunts ]
Oh , please , my baby ! Please give him to me !
- [ Crying ] - [ Mother Sobbing ]
Damn you !
[ Man Narrating ] When Michael Myers was six years old ,
he stabbed his sister to death .
For years he was locked up in Smith 's Grove Sanitarium ,
but he escaped .
And suddenly , Halloween became another word for mayhem .
One by one , he killed his entire family ...
until his nine-year-old niece , Jamie Lloyd ,
was the only one left alive .
Six years ago , Halloween night , Michael and Jamie vanished .
Many people believed them dead , but I think that someone hid them away .
Someone who keeps Michael , protects him ,
tries to control him .
And if there 's one thing I know , you can 't control evil .
You can lock it up , you can burn it and bury it and pray that it dies ,
but it never will .
It just rests awhile .
You can lock your doors and say your prayers at night ,
but the evil 's out there , waiting .
And maybe , just maybe ,
it 's closer than you think .
- [ Door Slams ] - Jamie !
- [ Crying ] - Come with me if you want to save your baby .
- [ Door Slams ] - [ Whimpers ] - God , he 's coming .
- [ Panting , Gasping ] - No ! Oh , God ! Come on !
It 's okay . Come on .
[ Whimpering ]
- Come on . - [ Baby Crying ]
- [ Panting ] - [ Baby Crying ]
Y ... It 's that way .
No . No !
Save your baby ! Go ! Now !
[ Baby Crying ]
- [ Whimpering ] - [ Water Dripping ]
[ Door Slams ]
Jamie ? [ Crying ]
[ Panting ]
[ Screaming , Choking , Gasping ]
[ Screaming , Choking ]
[ Baby Crying ]
- [ Door Slams ] - [ Thunderclap ]
[ Thunderclap ]
[ Baby Crying ]
[ Crying Continues ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Thunderclap ]
- Hey ! What 're you doin ' in my truck ? - [ Muffled Shouting ]
- What the hell are you doin in my truck ? What ? - [ Muffled Shouting ]
[ Shouting Continues ]
- What ? - [ Screams ]
[ Bone Cracks ]
- [ Gasps , Screaming ] - [ Engine Revs ]
- [ Thunder Rumbling ] - [ Panting ]
[ Tires Squeal ]
[ Thunderclap ]
[ Crow Cawing ]
- [ Deep Voice ] Danny . - [ Screaming ]
- [ Knife Unsheathing ] - Kill for him . - Mommy !
Danny ?
Mommy 's here . What is it , baby ?
The Voiceman . He 's here .
[ Mother ] No one 's there , sweetheart .
But I 've seen him ! He says things , bad things .
Like what ?
Okay .
[ Thunderclap ]
Mmm .
- Good night , Danny . - Good night , Mom .
[ Rain Falling ]
[ Man On Radio ] It 's Back Talk with Barry Simms .
We 're in the second hour of a special Halloween edition of Back Talk , and I 'm Barry Simms .
Tomorrow night , we will be coming to you from Haddonfield ,
the town that has banned Halloween since 1989 ...
when infamous serial killer Michael Myers and his niece , Jamie Lloyd ,
and about a dozen cops were killed in an explosion .
We have a caller waiting . Who 's next to talk to me ?
[ Female Caller ] Uh , I know this may sound crazy , Barry ,
but I really think I 'm in love with him .
He 's so untamed , so uninhibited .
- He 's everything I 've ever wanted in a man . - [ Barry ] Mm-hmm .
[ Barry ] You know , this is good . I can see the tabloids now .
" Psycho Lays Nympho : The Best Sex He Ever Dismembers . "
Is this the type you always fall for , lady ?
Any other serial studs on the list ? You know , Bundy ? Manson ?
What about that Dahmer guy ? I bet you could really cook with him .
[ Female Caller ] No , I just want Michael .
I wanna know what 's behind that mask .
[ Thunder Rumbling ]
[ Thunderclap ]
[ Barry ] Now , we 've got someone who actually claims to have seen that Michael Myers .
Come on . You 're on Back Talk next .
I was only eight years old when I saw him ,
but I was one of the lucky ones .
- [ Thunderclap ] - I survived .
[ Barry ] There is help out there for people like you .
It 's called electro-shock therapy ! Come on .
You don 't really believe that Michael Myers is actually alive .
Michael 's work isn 't done in Haddonfield .
And soon , very soon ,
- he 'll come home to kill again . - [ Thunderclap ]
But this time I 'll be ready .
[ Male Caller ] Michael Myers was not killed in that explosion ...
at the Haddonfield Police Station .
The CIA abducted Myers from his cell and killed everyone to cover up their tracks .
- [ Typewriter Keys Tapping ] - [ Barry ] Why would they do that ?
[ Caller ] That 's obvious . They wanted the ultimate assassin .
[ Barry ] Myers is now on the government payroll .
[ Caller ] No one controls Myers , not even the CIA .
He took out eight agents while they had him at Langley .
They couldn 't control him , so they packed him up in a rocket and shipped him off to space .
- Thank you . Thank you ! - [ Male Caller ] You don 't want to hear the facts , man !
- Thank you very much . - That 's the situation , is that the Cl ...
[ Barry Imitating Game Show Buzzer ] Michael Myers in space .
- Come on ! Next . - [ Male Caller # 2 ] Barry ,
what happened to that psychiatrist of his , Loomis ?
- I heard the old quack was dead . - Not dead . [ Laughing ]
Just very much retired .
[ Thunderclap ]
[ Knocking ]
[ Loomis ] Terence , come in .
What a night !
Not even so much as a sign for five miles on that road .
That 's the beauty of the countryside . I thrive on it .
[ Barry Continues On Radio ]
The lines are open , so give me your best shot ...
- at 1-800-968-7825 . - [ Jamie Whimpering ]
[ Thunderclap ]
[ Barry ] So who is responsible for getting ...
this Halloween rally thing together ?
[ Female Caller # 2 ] We are , the students of Haddonfield Junior College .
[ Barry ] But why go to all the trouble of throwing a soirée ?
So what if Halloween has been banned in Haddonfield ? Who gives a damn ?
[ Female Caller # 2 ] We do ! We live here . It 's time we got on with our lives .
That 's what tomorrow night is all about . This town is dying , Barry .
[ Barry ] I 've heard Michael Myers blamed for a lot of things tonight , but this is a first .
He 's actually killed the economy !
[ Female Caller # 2 ] Tomorrow night is going to change all that ,
especially after you do your broadcast live from campus .
[ Woman On Phone ] You have reached Haddonfield Emergency Services .
Due to severe weather conditions , all circuits are momentarily busy .
- If this is not an emergency ... - [ Female Caller # 2 ] Uh , yeah .
[ Barry ] You gonna get up there on the stage with old Bar ?
- [ Female Caller # 2 ] Uh , yeah , I will . - Yeah ?
Well , I 'll see you tomorrow night . This is Back Talk with Barry Simms .
Give me a call at 1-800-968-7825 .
That 's 1-800-YOU-SUCK .
So come on , all you boogeyman believers out there .
Give me a call . Call me tonight .
To old friends ,
- [ Chuckles ] - to retirement ,
to new beginnings .
Old friends .
Ahh !
Sam ,
I want you to come back to Smith 's Grove .
You should know that it 's not wise ...
- to play Halloween pranks on me . - It 's no prank .
You 're the one I 've chosen , Sam . I want you to come back .
I 've buried the ghosts . I 've buried them in this , this ...
manuscript .
I don 't want to practice medicine any more .
[ Jamie On Radio ] They 're coming ! They 're coming !
[ Barry ] They 're coming , they 're coming . Don 't tell me .
Your name is Joan ... Joan of Arc . You 're also hearing voices , right ?
[ Jamie Weeping ]
[ Barry ] Now , who 's coming ?
[ Jamie Gasping ] Michael .
Michael Myers .
Look , someone , anyone , help me . Dr. Loomis , are you out there ?
Can you hear me , Dr. Loomis ? I need your help .
[ Barry ] Please , please . No , no , stop that . What the hell is going on tonight ?
Every loony in the state is calling . What is this , a full moon ?
- [ Shuddering ] - I guess Halloween brings out all the wackos .
I can 't wait until we get to Haddonfield .
- [ Barry Continues ] - [ Young Man Talking ]
- [ Old Man Talking ] - [ Baby Crying ]
Shh , shh , shh , shh .
- [ Crying ] - Yes . It 's okay .
- You 're so good . - [ Electricity Buzzing ]
- [ Crying Continues ] - Shh , shh . Yes .
- It 's okay . - [ Crying Diminishes ]
[ Laughs ] Yes .
[ Door Slams ]
[ Whimpering ]
[ Thunderclap ]
[ Raspy Breathing ]
[ Engine Revving ]
[ Panting ]
No !
[ Engine Revving ]
[ Screaming ] Leave us alone !
[ Tires Screeching ]
[ Screams ]
[ Thunder Rumbling ]
[ Thunderclap ]
[ Grunts , Panting ]
[ Winces , Panting ]
[ Thunderclap ]
[ Exhales ]
[ Twigs Snap ]
No .
[ Choking , Shrieks ]
G ...
[ Gulps , Pants ]
[ Gurgling , Choking ]
[ Muttering ]
[ Grunts , Coughing ]
[ Grunting ]
You can 't have the baby , Michael .
You can 't have the baby .
- [ Motor Whirring ] - [ Screaming ]
[ Screaming , Whirring Continue ]
[ Screaming ]
Enough ...
of this Michael Myers ...
bullshit !
Now , you stinking kids got about three seconds ...
- to get the hell off my property ! - [ Kids Laughing ]
- One ! Two ! - [ Laughter Continues ]
[ Woman ] Doesn 't Danny look cute dressed up as his Uncle Tim ?
Great . Now I 've got a six-year-old gang member for a son .
Perfect .
This is the famous Tim Strode stomach pounder . You down for the challenge ?
Good try , Dan man . You better stick to orange juice .
Shitheads . Defacing my property .
Hmmph ! I showed them .
- John , they were just kids . - Kids , my dear Debra , are what 's ruining this country .
Everywhere you go it 's the same damn thing .
- There 's no goddamn respect . - Ahh ! [ Burps ]
I rest my case .
Kara , you 'll never pass that exam on an empty stomach .
" Cognitive therapy and emotional disorders . "
What are they teaching you in college these days ? The art of going crazy ?
It 's called psychology , Mom .
- Living in this house is enough to drive anyone crazy . - Oh , yeah ?
Well , who the hell asked you to come back here in the first place ?
I better get Danny to school .
Doesn 't show her face around her own family for five years ,
then expects us to roll out the red carpet .
You think going to college is gonna make up for your mistakes , girl ?
- [ Debra ] Would you please ... - Lay off her , Dad .
- Let 's go , Danny . - Kara , wait , please .
John , can 't we just sit down for once and try to be a family ?
Sorry , Mom .
Oh , yeah , that 's it , Debra . Just keep slipping her the cash .
While you 're at it , I got a great idea . Here .
Why don 't you give her all of our goddamn money ?
Why don 't you leave her alone ? Nothing ever changes , does it ?
When are you going to wake up ?
I got news for you , girl . Before you came around , everything was going fine .
Until you landed on our doorstep . [ Sighs ]
You and that little ... bastard of yours .
I see only one bastard in this house .
- [ Gasps ] - Get away from her !
- You shut up and stay outta this ! - John , please , don 't !
You ever talk to me like that again , and so help me God ... You understand ?
Give me the knife , Danny .
Eh ... Hey . Hey .
Make way for the Hardin County Express . Where 's Tim ?
We 're supposed to go over the list of events for tonight .
- Oh , God . - Another episode of Father Knows Best at the Strode house .
What the hell happened this time ? [ Gasps ]
- What 's gotten into you ? - Just glad to see you , that 's all .
- You guys okay ? - Tonight 's the night we bring some life back into this town .
Shit , Beth , why do we have to be the ones to organize this friggin ' fair ?
I mean , it 's only Halloween .
How many times do I have to tell you ?
- It 's not about Halloween . - [ Car Door Closes ]
- I love you , Danny . - I love you .
Give me a squeeze .
Mmm .
[ Sighs ]
[ Car Horn Honks ]
Yeah . Okay .
[ Sighs ]
Dr. Wynn , there 's something you should know .
Dawn , I 'd like you to get Dr. Loomis anything he needs ...
files , tests , records of every treatment we 've ever administered ...
to a former patient of ours , Michael Myers .
Michael Myers ?
Is something wrong ?
I just received a phone call . That girl , Jamie Lloyd ?
Her body was found this morning near Haddonfield .
Beth , who 's that guy who lives across the hall from you ?
Why , you interested ?
Yeah , right . He 's always staring out his window .
- Last night , I caught him watching me . - That must be Tommy .
On a weirdness scale of one to ten , he rates about a 13 .
Supposedly , some scary shit happened to him when he was a kid .
Messed up his head pretty bad . He 's harmless , though .
- He 's probably just lonely . - [ Tim ] Or horny .
- Something you probably haven 't felt in a while . - Tim !
Happy Halloween , Mrs. Blankenship !
Best part about living in that boardinghouse ...
is that crazy old lady wouldn 't hear a truck drive through her living room .
[ Jamie On Recorder ] You 've gotta listen to me !
- They 're coming ! They 're coming ! - [ Barry ] Mm-hmm , yeah .
So they 're coming , they 're coming . Don 't tell me . Your name is Joan ...
Joan of Arc . You 're also hearing voices , right ?
- [ Jamie Weeping ] - Come on . Now , who 's coming ?
[ Jamie ] It 's Michael . Michael Myers .
- [ Static ] - Look , someone , anyone , help me .
- Dr. Loomis , are you out there ? Can you hear me , Dr. L ... - [ Static , Recorder Stops ]
[ Voices Rewinding ]
- [ Static ] - [ Jamie ] It 's Michael . Michael Myers .
[ Bus Station Announcer ] ... your attention , please . Bus 611 from Pontiac ...
[ Jamie ] Look , someone , anyone , help me . Dr. Loomis , are you out there ?
- Can you hear me , Dr. Loomis ? I need your help . - [ Announcer Continues ]
- God , please , help . - [ Announcer ] May I have your attention , please ?
Bus 34 from Peoria , Russelville and Gardner ...
with through service to Chicago , Illinois ,
will be arriving in five minutes .
Ticketed passengers please wait inside the door ...
until arrival of bus number 34 .
Can I help you , sir ?
Can you tell me if a bus arrived from Pontiac last night ?
Sure did .
- Are you looking for someone ? - Thank you .
[ Baby Crying ]
[ Crying Continues ]
- [ Crying ] - Jesus .
[ Baby Coughing , Crying ]
Shh ! Shh , shh .
Shh ! Shh ! No . Shh , it 's okay .
- It 's okay . It 's okay . It 's okay , man . - [ Crying Continues ]
It 's okay . Shh , shh , shh , shh , shh .
[ Crying Continues ]
Shh !
[ Camera Shutter Clicking ]
[ Woman Talking On Police Radio ]
[ Wynn ] What 's that ?
It 's ... his mark . He 's come home .
[ Camera Shutter Clicks ]
♪ ♪ [ Rock Music On Radio ]
♪ Come and see me ♪
♪ Can 't you see me ♪ ♪
- ♪ ♪ [ Continues ] - Yo , check it out . Tonight 's gonna be killer .
Kara , I swear . One of these days , you 're gonna get lost in that thing .
L-I can 't find my term paper .
So copy someone else 's . I do it all the time . It works primo .
Oh , shit ! [ Sighs ]
Looks like your little boy has got himself quite an imagination .
He 's been having nightmares .
Ha-ha . I think it 's cool .
- Must be some nightmares . - [ Girl ] Beth , we got work to do .
Hey , are you gonna be okay ?
" Thorn " ?
I need to see a doctor .
- What seems to be the problem ? - Uh , it 's my baby .
- There 's been an accident . - What kind of accident ?
Get me a doctor , now !
- [ Phone Dial Pad Clicking ] - Security ?
- Dr. Loomis ? - Yeah .
Dr. Loomis , thank God you 're here .
I 'm sorry . I don 't know you , do I ?
I 'm Tommy . Tommy Doyle .
- Laurie Strode , Jamie 's mother , - [ Baby Crying ]
Was baby-sitting me the night when ...
Tommy Doyle . Uh ! What are you doing here ?
Please , I need to know the truth .
You heard her last night , didn 't you ?
Michael 's come home , hasn 't he ?
She is the last of his blood line .
- No , Dr. Loomis , she 's not the last . - [ Crying ]
Oh , God . There 's a family ...
relatives of the people who adopted Laurie ... the Strodes .
They 're living in the Myers house .
- Dr. Loomis , about Michael ... It 's just a theory of mine ... - [ Nurse ] That 's him .
Meet me ... tonight . 9 : 00 at the campus rally .
Uh ... Tommy , wait ! Wait !
[ Baby Crying ]
[ Dog Barking ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Washing Machine Humming ]
[ Washing Machine Chugging , Stops ]
[ Alarm Buzzing ]
[ Grunts ]
Great .
[ Creaking ]
Uh , Mrs ... Mrs. Strode , uh ...
- [ Panting ] - Is everything all right ?
- Who are you ? - I came to help your family .
[ Baby Crying ]
[ Crying Continues ]
Shh .
Shh ! It 's okay .
Okay .
Steven . You like that name ?
- [ Panting ] - Yeah , I think it suits you .
[ Baby Crying ]
[ Crying Continues ]
It 's okay . It 's all right .
- [ Grunts ] - I won 't let anything happen to you .
[ Cooing ]
[ Loomis ] This force , this thing that lived inside of him ...
came from a source too violent ,
too deadly for you to imagine .
It ... It grew inside him ,
contaminating his soul .
It was ... pure evil .
What makes you think he 'll come back here ?
This house is sacred to him . He has all his memories here .
His rage !
Mrs. Strode , I beg of you , don 't let your family ...
suffer the same fate that Laurie and her daughter suffered .
[ Bus Engine Roaring ]
- [ Children Giggling ] - ♪ ♪ [ Car Radio : Rock ]
[ Barry ] Uh , I 'm coming .
Yes , I 'm coming .
Get ready . Oh , yes ! Yes ! Yes !
Yes ! Yeah , I 'm coming , all right , and you 'd better be there .
The Halloween Harvest Fair . Let 's do it .
Sorry .
- [ Computer Keyboard Clicking ] - [ Phone Ringing ]
Strode Real Estate .
John , something terrible has happened .
- What do you want now , Debra ? - A man came by the house ,
a psychiatrist by the name of Loomis ,
and he told me about the terrible things that happened here in our house .
What the hell are you doing , talking to strangers , letting ' em in our house ?
John , they found Jamie Lloyd this morning . Somebody killed her .
[ John ] I don 't know what you 're talking about .
You gotta stop watching those damn TV talk shows .
I 'm getting the children out of here , at least until I know what 's going on .
John , I want you to come with us .
[ Scoffs ] You know ... You know , Debra , you 've lost it now .
You know that , Debra ? You 've just lost it .
The reason you moved us into this house ...
Your brother could never sell it because of what happened here , could he ?
And you knew .
And you didn 't tell us , John . You knew .
Goddammit !
[ Sighs ]
[ Panting ]
[ Debra 's Breathing Quickens ]
[ Phone Rings ]
[ Ringing ]
[ Panting ] Hello ?
- [ Voiceman ] We want the child . - Who is this ?
[ Phone Clicks Dead ]
[ Panting , Grunts ]
[ Panting ]
[ Gasps , Panting ]
[ Gasping ]
Huh !
[ Grunting , Panting ]
[ Panting ] Oh , Michael .
Mom ? I 'm home !
Hello ?
Mom !
[ Dog Barking ]
Mom ?
Danny ?
Mom ? Are you there ?
- What are you doing here ? - [ Gameboy Beeping ]
I 'm your neighbor from across the street , Tommy Doyle .
What are you doing with my son ? And where 's my mother ?
Uh ... She wasn 't here when Danny came home .
- Danny , go downstairs . - But Tommy 's my new friend .
He knows all about dinosaurs .
Do you know whose room this used to be ?
[ Door Latch Clicks ]
Hi , Mrs. B !
[ Baby Crying ]
Uh , you don 't really expect us to stay here , do you ?
I want you to watch your house . You can see everything from that window .
Do you know how insane this is ? Who am I supposed to be looking for ?
Him .
- [ Crying ] - Shh ! There .
- It 's okay . It 's okay , Steven . - [ Crying Continues ]
Ffffff !
- Kkffffff ! - [ Microwave Oven Beeping ]
Mommy !
Mom !
Not now , Danny .
- [ Baby Crying ] - [ Microwave Oven Beeps ]
- [ Sighs ] - [ Thunder Rumbling ]
- [ Crying Continues ] - [ Tommy ] Here you go .
- [ Crying Grows Louder ] - [ Tommy ] What ?
No . Come on , man .
[ Crying Continues ]
Here , l-let me try .
There .
- There . [ Chuckles ] - [ Crying Stops ]
- See ? All it takes is a mother 's touch . - [ Coughing ]
[ Tommy ] Runes are a kind of early alphabet ...
that originated about 500 B.C.
They were symbols carved out of stone ...
or pieces of wood ,
used in pagan rituals to portend future events and invoke magic .
Among the ancient druids , Thorn represented a demon ...
that spread sickness , brought death to hundreds of thousands of people .
According to Celtic legend , one child from each tribe ...
was chosen to be inflicted with the curse of Thorn ...
to offer the blood sacrifices of its next of kin ...
- on the night of Samhain . - Halloween .
The sacrifice of one family meant sparing the lives of an entire tribe .
For years I 've been convinced there must be some reason ,
some method behind Michael 's madness .
The druids were also great mathematicians and astronomers ,
but the Thorn symbol is actually a constellation of stars ...
that appears from time to time on Halloween night .
Whenever it appears , he appears .
[ Tommy Tapping Keyboard ] Coincidence ?
- [ Cries ] - I think that 's why these people ,
whoever they are , are after Jamie 's baby .
- [ Crying ] - To make it Michael 's final sacrifice .
[ Cries Softly ]
Where are you going ?
- To find the only man who can stop him before it 's too late . - Oh , no . Where 's Danny ?
- Danny ? Danny ! - Mrs. Blankenship !
- Oh ! - Have you seen ...
Danny , don 't ever walk off without telling me where you 're going !
Take him upstairs . Lock the door and wait ' til I get back .
And , Kara , whatever you do ,
don 't go back to your house .
During the autopsy we found this . It 's placental fluid .
- You mean to say th ... - I estimate she gave birth no more than 24 hours ago .
Then the question is , where is the baby ?
I think I ... I may already know .
[ Siren Wailing In Distance ]
[ Crickets Chirping ]
Do you know why we celebrate Halloween ?
Because that 's when we go trick-or-treating and get candy .
Oh , well , yes , but ... a long , long time ago ...
it was a night of great power ...
when the days grew short ...
and the spirits of the dead returned to their homes ...
to warm themselves by the fireside .
All across the land , huge bonfires were lit .
Oh , there was a marvelous celebration .
People danced and they played games ...
and they dressed up in costumes ,
hoping to ward off the evil spirits ,
especially ...
- the boogeyman . - [ Thunderclap ]
What 's the boogeyman ?
- Come on , Danny . Say good night to Mrs. Blankenship . - Good night , Mrs. Blankenship .
He hears the voice , you know . Just like the other boy that lived in that house .
[ Thunderclap ]
- What are you talking about ? - I was baby-sitting with him that night ...
little Mikey Myers that lived across the street ...
and that 's when the voice came , the night he murdered his sister .
Michael heard a voice ?
It told him to kill his family .
[ Thunderclap ]
[ Students Shouting , Chattering ]
- Where the hell 's Barry ? Let 's go ! - Don 't get star-struck on me now .
We got a real agenda here , and Barry is gonna help us get the message out .
[ Beth ] Hey , look .
Helloooo , Haddonfield !
[ Crowd Cheering , Hooting ]
- Barry ! - [ Announcer ] WKNB presents ...
Back Talk with Barry Simms ,
- live from Haddonfield , Illinois , the home ... - Barry !
- of Michael Myers ! - [ Crowd Hooting , Shouting ]
- [ Engine Revs ] - [ John ] Whoopee !
[ Laughing ]
Debra ! I 'm home !
Thanks for the dinner .
We ... Come out , come out , wherever you are .
Goddammit . She actually left .
I know what 's going on . [ Chuckles ]
It must be ... the boogeyman .
Ha ! Here I come , boogeyman .
'Cause , you know , I am really scared .
- [ Sighs ] - [ Washing Machine Chugging ]
[ Washing Machine Chugging ]
[ Thunderclap ]
[ Water Sloshing ]
[ Chugging Continues ]
[ Chugging ]
What the hell ? The power 's off .
[ Machine Stops ]
[ Groans , Grunting ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Screaming Continues ]
- [ Screaming Continues ] - [ Electricity Crackling ]
[ Gurgling , Choking ]
Tell me , kids , how 's it feel to finally pull Halloween ...
out of the proverbial Haddonfield closet ?
What we 're saying here is we will no longer ...
let the powers that be control our minds .
For years , Halloween has represented everything that 's wrong with Haddonfield .
But Michael Myers is long gone .
There is no boogeyman !
Whoa !
Does she get this riled up in the sack , Tim ?
I bet she wears crotchless panties and barks like a dog .
Beth , what do you say , honey ? You and me , uh ...
[ Beth Scoffs ]
As I was saying , we have to stop acting out of fear .
Just look at Tim 's family . They live in the Myers house .
- You do ? - We do ?
Uh ... yeah , we do . Great house .
- Hmm . I see . - Strong wood .
You mean to tell me you actually live ...
in the house of the most brutal mass murderer in history ?
This is The Barry Simms Show .
And when we return , we 'll be comin ' at you live ...
from the one , the only Myers house .
How 's that for a Halloween shock-fest ? Woo-ahh !
- How far to your house ? - Half a mile . But I don 't know if my folks ...
Good . I 'll meet you there in five .
- What about the kids ? We 're supposed to throw candy . - Phone !
Relax your crack , sweetheart . Quick tootle around the old household and we 'll be back .
Pull the van out back so that I can sneak out of here nice and quietly .
Oh , no . No , no , really . You 're too good to me .
Thanks for putting me in the middle of this cheap-shit country bumpkin outfit , Paul .
I really appreciate it . My fans expect better than this .
You tell that penny-pinching whiner Mike Sarducci ...
that when I get back , I 'm gonna cut off his balls ...
and wear ' em as earrings .
Where 's the goddamn van ? God !
Oh , no , I 'm trotting ' out for a cheeseburger .
I 'm taking the show to the real Myers house ...
where we should have gone in the first place !
Ten minutes in that house and I 'll have every fruitcake medium in the country ...
calling in trying to channel the spirit of that pussy , Michael Myers .
[ Chuckling ] Sure we can do another show about him .
Kick the audience in the face enough , and they 'll lick you all over .
I 'll call ya later . Bye-bye .
Where the fuck ... [ Grunting ]
- [ Grunting , Gagging ] - [ Tearing Sounds ]
[ Clicking Switch ]
What happened to the lights ?
You really think Barry 's gonna show up ?
Let 's hope not .
Sorry he turned out to be such an asshole .
It 's okay .
Where is everyone ? Mom ? Kara ?
They 're probably at the fair , which is where we should be .
Beth , um , what you said before about Michael Myers living in our house ?
Is that really true ?
It was a cold Halloween night .
He stood in the shadows watching through the windows ...
as his sister and her boyfriend made love .
Then he crept inside , picked up a butcher knife ,
she turned around ... and he stabbed her !
- Cut it out , Beth ! - [ Thunderclap ]
I really didn 't know that Michael Myers lived in my house , okay ?
It freaks me out .
I 'm sorry .
I was just foolin ' around .
It 's okay .
- Let 's get the candles . - Just a minute .
[ Children Shouting , People Chattering ]
[ Little Girl ] Mommy , it 's raining .
It 's raining red .
Mommy , it 's raining red .
It 's raining .
[ People Shouting , Chattering ]
It 's warm .
[ Drop Of Liquid Splattering ]
[ Tree Branches Creaking ]
[ Branches Creaking ]
[ Little Girl Screaming ]
[ Children Screaming ]
[ Loomis ] Tommy !
Dr. Loomis , it 's happening .
Where 's the baby ?
[ Both Moaning ]
[ Exhales ]
Your sister would kill us if she knew we did it in her bed .
Hey , it was your idea .
I am bad , aren 't I ?
Only when you wear crotchless panties and bark like a dog .
[ Both Laugh ]
[ Sighing ]
- Where you goin ' ? - I gotta take a shower .
- You know , to stay fresh . - [ Giggling ]
Watch out for the boogeyman .
[ Thunderclap ]
Hey , Beth , can you bring a towel in here . I 'm freezing .
Where are you when I need you , honey ?
[ Shower Curtain Rustling ]
Thanks . I 'll be in in a minute .
[ Gagging ]
Mommy ?
Hold on a second , Danny .
[ Voiceman ] Danny .
[ Phone Ringing ]
- Hello . - Mom ? Wait ... Who is this ?
- No , this is Beth . - What are you doing there ?
Do you know where my mother is ?
- She 's not home . No one is . What 's wrong ? - Is Tim with you ?
He 's in the shower .
I 'm across the street . I can see you .
I want you to listen to me . Get Tim and get out of that house now .
- Kara , what is going on ? - Beth , look out ! There 's someone right behind you !
- [ Knife Striking ] - [ Gasping ]
- [ Gasping ] - [ Beth Screaming ]
- [ Screaming ] - [ Knife Striking ]
No !
No ! Danny , no !
Danny !
Danny .
[ Panting ]
[ Labored Breathing ]
- [ Gasping ] - [ Distant Scream ]
[ Sobbing ]
Danny ?
Oh .
[ Poker Clanks On Floor ]
Danny ?
- Danny ? - Mommy ?
It 's okay .
Danny , run !
[ Thunderclap ]
[ Kara Screams ]
Danny ?
Don 't move .
Stay right there .
I 'll come and get you .
[ Screams ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Whimpering ]
The baby . Where 's the baby ?
[ Kara ] Please , open the door !
Please , open the door !
[ Thunderclap ]
Please , Tommy , help us !
[ Pounding On Door ]
Help us , please !
[ Panting ] Help us , please !
[ Pounding ]
Get ' em upstairs ! Now !
- Where 's the baby ? - He 's gone .
- Who else knew I had the baby ? - No one .
No . There had to be someone else .
- Who knew ? - Nobody knew except me and ...
[ Voiceman ] Danny , come to me .
[ Wind Whistling ]
- Danny , no . - [ Thunderclap ]
No , please .
Careful with the girl .
- [ Thunderclap ] - Kara !
Wynn .
Mrs. Blankenship ! Oh , God , hurry ! We have to ...
Hello , dear .
[ Screams ]
[ Tommy ] Where is she ? Where 's Kara ?
- I feel like I 've been drugged . - We have been drugged .
Why are they doing this ?
Why didn 't they just kill us ?
It 's his game ...
and I know where he wants to play it .
[ Panting ]
[ Groans ]
[ Woman Screaming ]
[ Brakes Squealing , Doors Opening , Closing ]
- [ Cocks Gun ] - [ Snickers ]
- Dr. Loomis , you know that can 't stop Michael . - Nothing will stop Michael .
But Wynn ...
- Dr. Loomis ... - You stay here .
Don 't go anywhere until I come back .
Wynn . Huh .
- [ Door Opening ] - Ah ! [ Chuckling ]
I was getting worried , Sam . I was afraid you wouldn 't make it .
[ Woman Screaming ]
Why ... now ?
Because you were the first one to see it ,
and you recognized its power .
- Michael ? - Evil .
Pure ... uncorrupted ... ancient .
You ...
are ... a madman .
I 've had my failures , but this baby ... Jamie 's baby ...
We are at the dawn of a new age , Sam .
And I 'm asking you to join me .
I thought ...
- Michael was a monster , but you ... - [ Thud ]
[ Grunting ]
We 're ready for you , Dr. Wynn .
Good .
Well , we 'll give Dr. Loomis a little time to think about it .
[ Snickers ] Maximum security .
[ Woman Screaming ]
[ Door Knob Rattling ]
Kara ?
- Kara . - [ Shrieking ]
He walks amongst us , brother .
He 's come back and ...
he 's very angry .
How does it feel to be damned ?
Oh ... [ Panting ]
Oh , shit .
Tommy ?
Tommy , is that you ?
Kara !
- Tommy ? - Kara ! Kara !
I 'm in here !
- Are you there ? - Get back !
[ Grunting ]
Tommy ?
Tommy ? Are you okay ?
Tommy , are you okay ?
[ Grunting ]
Oh ! Oh ! Oh , God ! Stop !
Oh , God ! Ohhh ! Ahhh !
Let go of me !
[ Steam Hissing ]
[ Hinge Squeaking ]
[ Woman Speaking , Indistinct ]
[ People Talking , Indistinct ]
- I 've never seen genetic engineering on this scale . - [ Woman ] Exactly .
The recombinant DNA repercussions alone make this procedure a breakthrough .
[ Man ] Especially the splicing instruments .
It 's based on Dr. Wynn 's research .
[ Wynn ] Okay , okay , okay . You can take that off now .
Halloween is over . [ Chuckling ]
I want to talk to you about this research .
[ Indistinct Talking ]
Will someone do a quick check on him , please ?
[ Baby Fussing ]
[ Baby Crying ]
There 's Danny .
[ Both Grunting ]
[ Panting ]
[ Door Opening ]
[ Heavy Breathing ]
[ Door Closing ]
[ Clattering ]
[ Screaming , Crashing ]
[ Man Groaning , Gagging ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Tommy ] Run !
Danny , come on !
[ Man Screaming ]
Oh , God !
[ Panting ] Run ! Come on , Danny !
[ Wailing ]
[ Whimpering ] God !
[ Groaning ]
[ Screaming ]
- The steam room ! - Go ahead !
H-Help me , please ! Help me ! Help !
[ Screaming , Grunting ]
[ Screaming , Bones Crunching ]
Go , go , go , go !
Fuck !
[ Tommy ] Go ! Go !
Quick , in here ! It locks !
[ Panting ]
Go ! Go !
[ Tommy ] Mike ?
You 've won .
[ Chuckles ]
[ Heavy Breathing ]
[ Chuckling ]
He 's yours .
[ Heavy Breathing ]
[ Baby Crying ]
[ Tommy Grunting ]
[ Gagging ]
Uhhh !
[ Kara Grunting ]
[ Grunting Continues ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Gasping ]
[ Gagging ]
[ Danny ] Leave her alone !
[ Gasps ]
Mommy ! [ Whimpering ] Mom ! Mom !
Help ! Mommy ! Mommy !
Mommy ! Mom !
- Mom ! Help ! - Danny !
[ Loomis ] Get in there ! Go on ! Get in !
[ Danny ] Mommy !
- Come with us . - No , l-I have a ...
little business to attend to here .
[ Chains Rattling ]
[ Man Screaming ]
[ Wind Whistling ]
♪ Come and see me ♪
♪ Can 't you see me ♪
♪ It 's so easy ♪
♪ To believe in you ♪
♪ I believed in you ♪
♪ Your intention ♪
♪ My addiction ♪
♪ Fear no evil ♪
♪ You 'll be safe in here ♪
♪ I was saved in here ♪
♪ And fools shine on ♪
♪ Where fools shine on ♪
♪ Come and see me ♪
♪ Can 't you see me ♪
♪ You 'll be saved in here ♪
♪ And fools shine on ♪
♪ here fools shine on ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ And fools shine on ♪
♪ Where fools shine on ♪ ♪